Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of Yearbooks MC.304
New York University Archives
New York University Archives Collection of Yearbooks
1887-2012
New York University Archives
New York University
MC.304
86.41 Linear Feet in 527 items, 93 manuscript boxes, 2 tall manuscript boxes, and 1 folder in a shared flat oversize box
This assembled collection contains yearbooks dating from 1887 to 2012 which were published by New York University (NYU) and its component schools. These yearbooks document the graduating seniors and underclassmen, administrators and faculty, athletic teams, and student clubs and organizations. Contents of the yearbooks vary, but can include graduating senior descriptions which contain individual activity lists and photographic portraits; school calendars; local business advertisements; as well as historical information and images for: underclassmen, faculty, administrators, athletic teams, and student organizations. While this collection is extensive, it is not comprehensive, and there may be published yearbooks that are not included in this collection. This collection also includes a small number of student directories and registers containing names and photographs of incoming freshman, graduate students, and law students.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; provenance is unknown. Additional items were donated by various individuals between 2018 and 2023; the accession numbers associated with these gifts are 2019.059, 2019-060, 2019.078, 2020.004, 2020.020, 2022.036, 2022.080, and 2023.038.
Existence and Location of Copies
Additional duplicate copies of yearbooks are in the New York University Publications (preservation copies) (RG 1.0).
Appraisal
In September 2025 a Graduate School of Public Administration Yearbook for 1974-1975 was removed from the collection because it was incomplete.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into series which are based on the New York University Archives record group classification system. Titles for the record groups are based on the school or program's official name (as of 2019). For example, School of Commerce yearbooks are included as part of the Stern School of Business record group.
Yearbooks are arranged within the record groups by title and chronologically within.
Historical Note
Although the earliest yearbook in this collection dates to 1887, the University did not start regularly producing yearbooks until the 1890s. The University's various component schools started issuing yearbooks for their own student bodies starting in the early 20th century.
As of 2019, NYU is no longer producing yearbooks.
Scope and Contents
This assembled collection contains New York University (NYU) yearbooks dating from 1887 to 2012. The yearbooks contain information on graduating and underclass students from various campuses, colleges, and schools across the university system including dentistry, medicine, business, education, the performing arts, and law.
Up until 1907, students from different campuses and schools were combined into a single yearbook; for example The Lyre and The Violet. Student inclusion in the yearbook was voluntary and they were not required to sit for a portrait or submit personal information. As a result, some yearbooks may have a page that lists students that were not pictured.
A variety of student information is included in yearbooks, documenting their involvement in clubs, athletic teams, or student government positions. Photographs of individuals and student organizations and teams are in the yearbooks; however, group photographs rarely include names or identifications. Evening, part-time, and graduate students are infrequently pictured in yearbooks, except in rare instances in school-specific editions. There are local business advertisements in the yearbooks as well.
Coverage of spring sports (e.g., baseball, soccer, track and field) often appears in the following year's yearbook. For example, the 1934 baseball season may be featured in the 1935 Album. In the late 19th and early 20th centuries the junior class was responsible for producing the yearbooks for The Violet and The Commerce Violet. As a result, covers of these yearbooks often display the junior class's expected graduation year instead of the actual year of publication (which is the year the senior class was graduating). This discrepancy between cover date and senior content date can lead to confusion. Researchers are encouraged to consult yearbooks from adjacent years to ensure complete coverage of a specific class.
During the late 19th century through the mid-20th century, the yearbooks often contain "grinds" which would include student nicknames and inside jokes meant to be poking fun at the individual. Users should use caution when viewing these "grinds" which could potentially contain harmful language and stereotypes that reflect the racism and sexism common in the time they were written.
Additionally, this collection contains photographic directories and registers for the incoming freshmen/class members for some NYU schools and divisions.
While the collection is extensive, it is not comprehensive, and there may be published yearbooks that are not included in this collection. Some schools such as GSAS (Graduate School of Arts and Sciences), SPS (School of Professional Studies), and the College of Veterinary Medicine do not appear to have produced yearbooks.
Student activities.; College sports.; College yearbooks; School yearbooks.; College students -- New York (N.Y.)
- All-University (RG 1), 1887
  - The Lyre, 1887
    - User Copy, 1887 (Item 1)
- University College of Arts and Science and the College of Engineering (University Heights) (RG 18 and RG 24), 1890-1973
  - The Violet, 1890
    Historical Note
    Produced by the Class of 1891 for the Class of 1890
    - User Copy, 1890 (Item 2)
  - The Violet, circa 1891
    Produced by the Class of 1892 for the Class of 1891
    - User Copy, circa 1891 (Item 3)
  - The Violet, circa 1892
    Produced by the Class of 1893 for the Class of 1892
    - User Copy, circa 1892 (Item 4)
  - The Violet, May 1893
    Produced by the Class of 1894 for the Class of 1893
    - User Copy, 1893 (Item 5)
  - The Violet, April 1894
    Produced by the Class of 1895 for the Class of 1894
    - User Copy, April 1894 (Item 6)
  - The Violet, May 1895
    Produced by the Class of 1896 for the Class of 1895
    - User Copy, May 1895 (Item 7)
  - The Violet, May 1896
    Produced by the Class of 1897 for the Class of 1896
    - User Copy, 1896 (Item 8)
  - The Violet, 1897
    Produced by the Class of 1898 for the Class of 1897.
    Scope and Contents
    This yearbook was produced in two different cover colors: white and red.
    - User Copy, 1897 (Item 9, Item 10)
  - The Violet, 1898
    Likely produced by the Class of 1899 for the Class of 1898
    - User Copy, 1898 (Item 11)
  - The Violet, 1899
    Produced by the Class of 1900 for the Class of 1899
    - User Copy, 1899 (Item 12)
  - The Violet, circa 1900
    Produced by the Class of 1901 for the Class of 1900
    - User Copy, circa 1900 (Item 99)
  - The Violet, circa 1901
    Produced by the Class of 1902 for the Class of 1901
    - User Copy, circa 1901 (Item 13)
  - The Violet, circa 1902
    Produced by the Class of 1903 for the Class of 1902
    - User Copy, circa 1902 (Item 14)
  - The Violet, circa 1903
    Produced by the Class of 1904 for the Class of 1903
    - User Copy, circa 1903 (Item 15)
  - The Violet, circa 1904
    Produced by the Class of 1905 for the Class of 1904
    - User Copy, circa 1904 (Item 16)
  - The Violet, circa 1905
    Produced by the Class of 1906 for the Class of 1905
    - User Copy, circa 1905 (Item 17)
  - The Violet, circa 1906
    Biographical / Historical
    Produced by the Class of 1907 for the Class of 1906
    - User Copy, circa 1906 (Item 18)
  - The Violet, circa 1907
    Likely produced by the Class of 1908 for the Class of 1907
    - User Copy, circa 1907 (Item 19)
  - The Violet, circa 1908
    Produced by the Class of 1909 for the Class of 1908
    - User Copy, circa 1908 (Item 20)
  - The Violet, circa 1909
    Likely produced by the Class of 1910 for the Class of 1909
    - User Copy, circa 1909 (Item 21)
  - The Violet, circa 1910
    Produced by the Class of 1911 for the Class of 1910
    - User Copy, circa 1910 (Item 22)
  - The Violet, circa 1911
    Produced by the Class of 1912 for the Class of 1911
    - User Copy, circa 1911 (Item 586)
  - The Violet, circa 1912
    Likely produced by the Class of 1913 for the Class of 1912
    - User Copy, circa 1912 (Item 23)
  - The Violet, circa 1913
    Produced by the Class of 1914 for the Class of 1913
    - User Copy, circa 1913 (Item 24)
  - The Violet, circa 1914
    Produced by the Class of 1915 for the Class of 1914
    - User Copy, circa 1914 (Item 25)
  - The Violet, circa 1915
    Produced by the Class of 1916 for the Class of 1915
    - User Copy, circa 1915 (Item 26)
  - The Violet, circa 1916
    Produced by the Class of 1917 for the Class of 1916
    - User Copy, circa 1916 (Item 27)
  - The Violet, circa 1917
    Produced by the Class of 1918 for the Class of 1917
    - User Copy, circa 1917 (Item 28)
  - The Violet, 1918
    Produced by the Class of 1919 for the Class of 1918
    - User Copy, 1918 (Item 29)
  - The Violet, circa 1919
    Produced by the Class of 1920 for the Class of 1919
    - User Copy, circa 1919 (Item 30)
  - The Violet, circa 1920
    Produced by the Class of 1921 for the Class of 1920
    - User Copy, circa 1920 (Item 31)
  - The Violet, circa 1921
    Produced by the Class of 1922 for the Class of 1921
    - User Copy, circa 1921 (Item 32)
  - The Violet, 1922
    Produced by the Class of 1923 for the Class of 1922
    - User Copy, 1922 (Item 33)
  - The Violet, circa 1923
    Produced by the Class of 1924 for the Class of 1923
    - User Copy, circa 1923 (Item 34)
  - The Violet, 1924
    Produced by the Class of 1925 for the Class of 1924
    - User Copy, 1924 (Item 35)
  - The Violet, 1925
    Produced by the Class of 1926 for the Class of 1925
    - User Copy, 1925 (Item 36)
  - The Violet, 1926
    Produced by the Class of 1927 for the Class of 1926
    - User Copy, 1926 (Item 37)
  - The Violet, 1927
    Produced by the Class of 1928 for the Class of 1927
    - User Copy, 1927 (Item 38)
  - The Violet, 1928
    Produced by the Class of 1929 for the Class of 1928
    - User Copy, 1928 (Item 39)
  - The Violet, 1929
    Produced by the Class of 1930 for the Class of 1929
    - User Copy, 1929 (Item 40)
  - The Violet, 1930
    Produced by the Class of 1931 for the Class of 1930
    - User Copy, 1930 (Item 41)
  - The Violet, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 42)
  - The Violet, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Item 43)
  - The Violet, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 44)
  - The Violet, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Item 45)
  - The Violet, 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Item 46)
  - The Violet, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 47)
  - The Violet, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 48)
  - The Violet, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 49)
  - The Violet, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 50)
  - The Violet, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 51)
  - The Violet, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 52)
  - The Violet, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 53)
  - The Violet, 1944
    - User Copy, 1944 (Item 54)
  - The Violet, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Item 55)
  - The Violet, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Item 56)
  - The Violet, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 57)
  - The Violet, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 58)
  - The Violet, 1949
    - User Copy, 1949 (Item 59)
  - The Violet, 1950
    - User Copy, 1950 (Item 60)
  - The Violet, 1951
    - User Copy, 1951 (Item 61)
  - The Violet, 1952
    - User Copy, 1952 (Item 62)
  - The Violet, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 63)
  - The Violet, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 64)
  - The Violet, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 65)
  - The Violet, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 66)
  - The Violet, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 67)
  - The Violet, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 68)
  - The Violet, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 69)
  - The Violet, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 587)
  - The Violet, 1961
    - User Copy, 1961 (Item 70)
  - The Violet, 1962
    - User Copy, 1962 (Item 71)
  - The Violet, 1963
    - User Copy, 1963 (Item 72)
  - The Violet, 1964
    - User Copy, 1964 (Item 73)
  - The Violet, 1965
    - User Copy, 1965 (Item 74)
  - The Violet, 1966
    - User Copy, 1966 (Item 75)
  - The Violet, 1967
    - User Copy, 1967 (Item 76)
  - The Violet, 1968
    - User Copy, 1968 (Item 588)
  - The Violet, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 77)
  - The Violet, 1970
    This yearbook has two versions with different lengths and cover colors (red and blue).
    - User Copy, 1970 (Item 78, Item 729)
  - The Violet, 1971
    - User Copy, 1971 (Item 79)
  - The Violet, 1972
    - User Copy, 1972 (Item 80)
  - The Violet, 1973
    - User Copy, 1973 (Item 81)
- College of Arts and Sciences (Washington Square) (RG 19), 1922-2005
  - The Album, 1922
    - User Copy, 1922 (Item 82)
  - The Album, circa 1923
    - User Copy, circa 1923 (Item 399)
  - The Album, 1924
    - User Copy, 1924 (Item 83)
  - The Album, 1925
    - User Copy, 1925 (Item 84)
  - The Album, 1927
    - User Copy, 1927 (Item 85)
  - The Senior Album, 1927
    - User Copy, 1927 (Item 86)
  - The Album, 1928
    - User Copy, 1928 (Item 87)
  - The Album, 1929
    - User Copy (Item 88)
  - The Album, 1930
    - User Copy, 1930 (Item 89)
  - The Album, 1931
    - User Copy, 1931 (Item 90)
  - The Album, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 91)
  - The Album, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Item 92)
  - The Album, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 93)
  - The Album, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Item 94)
  - The Album, 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Item 95)
  - The Album, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 96)
  - The Album, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 764)
  - The Album, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 97)
  - The Album, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 98)
  - The Album, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 100)
  - The Album, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 101)
  - The Album, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 102)
  - The Album, 1944
    - User Copy, 1944 (Item 103)
  - The Album, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Item 104)
  - The Album, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Item 105)
  - The Album, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 106)
  - The Album, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 107)
  - The Album, 1949
    - User Copy, 1949 (Item 108)
  - The Album, 1950
    - User Copy, 1950 (Item 109)
  - The Album, 1951
    - User Copy, 1951 (Item 110)
  - The Album, 1952
    - User Copy, 1952 (Item 111)
  - The Album, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 112)
  - The Album, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 113)
  - The Album, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 114)
  - The Album, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 115)
  - The Album, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 116)
  - The Album, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 117)
  - The Album, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 118)
  - The Album, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 119)
  - The Album, 1961
    - User Copy, 1961 (Item 120)
  - The Album, 1962
    - User Copy, 1962 (Item 121)
  - The Album, 1963
    - User Copy, 1963 (Item 122)
  - The Album, 1964
    - User Copy, 1964 (Item 123)
  - The Album, 1965
    - User Copy, 1965 (Item 124)
  - The Album, 1966
    - User Copy, 1966 (Item 125)
  - The Album, 1967
    - User Copy, 1967 (Item 126)
  - The Album, 1968
    - User Copy, 1968 (Item 127)
  - The Album, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 128)
  - The Album, 1973
    - User Copy, 1973 (Item 129)
  - The Album, 1974
    - User Copy, 1974 (Item 130)
  - The Album, 1975
    - User Copy, 1975 (Item 131)
  - The Album, 1976
    - User Copy, 1976 (Item 132)
  - The Torch, 1977
    - User Copy, 1977 (Item 133)
  - The Torch, 1978
    - User Copy, 1978 (Item 134)
  - The Torch Supplement, 1979
    There was no Torch published for this year. The 1980 Torch included a supplement for the graduating class of 1979.
    - User Copy, 1979 (Box 1, Item 135)
  - The Torch, 1980
    - User Copy, 1980 (Item 136)
  - The Torch, 1981
    - User Copy, 1981 (Item 137)
  - The Torch, 1982
    - User Copy, 1982 (Item 138)
  - The Torch, 1983
    - User Copy, 1983 (Item 139)
  - The Torch, 1984
    - User Copy, 1984 (Item 140)
  - The Torch, 1985
    - User Copy, 1985 (Item 141)
  - The Torch, 1986
    - User Copy, 1986 (Item 589)
  - The Torch, 1987
    - User Copy, 1987 (Item 142)
  - The Torch, 1988
    - User Copy, 1988 (Item 143)
  - The Torch, 1989
    - User Copy, 1989 (Item 144)
  - The Torch, 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Item 145)
  - The Torch, 1991
    - User Copy, 1991 (Item 146)
  - The Torch, 1992
    - User Copy, 1992 (Item 147)
  - The Torch, 1993
    - User Copy, 1993 (Item 148)
  - The Torch, 1994
    - User Copy, 1994 (Item 149)
  - The Torch, 1995
    - User Copy, 1995 (Item 150)
  - The Torch, 1998
    - User Copy, 1998 (Item 151)
  - The Torch, 1999
    - User Copy, 1999 (Item 152)
  - The Torch, 2000
    - User Copy, 2000 (Item 153)
  - The Torch, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Item 154)
  - CAS Yearbook Spring Supplement, 2001
    - User Copy, 2001 (Box 1, Item 155)
  - The Torch, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Item 156)
  - CAS Yearbook Spring Supplement, 2002
    - User Copy, 2002 (Box 1, Item 157)
  - The Torch, 2003
    - User Copy, 2003 (Item 158)
  - CAS Yearbook Spring Supplement, 2003
    - User Copy, 2003 (Box 1, Item 159)
  - The Torch, 2004
    - User Copy, 2004 (Item 160)
  - The Torch, 2005
    - User Copy, 2005 (Item 161)
  - The Freshman Register, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 585)
  - The Freshman Register, 1987
    - User Copy, 1987 (Item 162)
  - The Freshman Register, 1988
    - User Copy, 1988 (Item 163)
  - The Freshman Register, 1989
    - User Copy, 1989 (Item 164)
  - The Freshman Register, 1990
    - User Copy, 1990 (Item 165)
  - The Freshman Register, 1991
    - User Copy, 1991 (Item 166)
  - The Freshman Register, 1993
    - User Copy, 1993 (Box 1, Item 167)
  - The Freshman Register, 1994
    - User Copy, 1994 (Box 1, Item 168)
- The Evening Division of Washington Square College (RG 19.13), 1930-1932
  - The Owl, 1930
    - User Copy, 1930 (Item 169)
  - The Owl, 1931
    - User Copy, 1931 (Item 170)
  - The Owl, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 171)
- School of Law (RG 22), 1953-1981
  - Certiorari Writ, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 172)
  - Certiorari Writ, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 173)
  - Certiorari Writ, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 174)
  - Certiorari Writ, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 175)
  - Certiorari Writ, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 176)
  - Certiorari Writ, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 177)
  - The Class Book, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 178)
  - The Yearbook, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 179)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1972-1973
    - User Copy, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Item 180)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1973-1974
    - User Copy, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Item 181)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1974-1975
    - User Copy, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Item 182)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1975-1976
    - User Copy, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Item 183)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1976-1977
    - User Copy, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Item 184)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1977-1978
    - User Copy, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Item 185)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1978-1979
    - User Copy, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Item 186)
  - School of Law First-Year Students Portrait Booklet, 1979-1980
    - User Copy, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Item 187)
  - School of Law Graduate Division Portrait Booklet, 1975-1976
    - User Copy, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Item 188)
  - School of Law Graduate Division Portrait Booklet, 1978-1979
    - User Copy, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Item 189)
  - School of Law Graduate Division Portrait Booklet, 1979-1980
    - User Copy, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Item 190)
  - School of Law Graduate Division Portrait Booklet, 1980-1981
    - User Copy, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Item 191)
- School of Medicine (RG 23), 1922-2012
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1922
    - User Copy, 1922 (Item 191)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1925
    - User Copy, 1925 (Box 1, Item 192)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1926
    - User Copy, 1926 (Item 193)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1927
    - User Copy, 1927 (Item 194)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1928
    - User Copy, 1928 (Item 195)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1929
    - User Copy, 1929 (Item 196)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1930
    - User Copy, 1930 (Item 197)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1931
    - User Copy, 1931 (Item 198)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1932
    - User Copy, 1932 (Item 199)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1933
    - User Copy, 1933 (Item 200)
  - The Bellevue Violet, 1934
    - User Copy, 1934 (Item 201)
  - The Medical Violet, 1935
    - User Copy, 1935 (Item 202)
  - The Medical Violet, 1936
    - User Copy, 1936 (Item 203)
  - The Medical Violet, 1937
    - User Copy, 1937 (Item 590)
  - The Medical Violet, 1938
    - User Copy, 1938 (Item 204)
  - The Medical Violet, 1939
    - User Copy, 1939 (Item 205)
  - The Medical Violet, 1940
    - User Copy, 1940 (Item 206)
  - The Medical Violet, 1941
    - User Copy, 1941 (Item 207)
  - The Medical Violet, 1942
    - User Copy, 1942 (Item 208)
  - The Medical Violet, 1943
    - User Copy, 1943 (Item 209)
  - The Medical Violet, 1944
    - User Copy, 1944 (Item 210)
  - The Medical Violet, 1945
    - User Copy, 1945 (Item 211)
  - The Medical Violet, 1946
    - User Copy, 1946 (Item 212)
  - The Medical Violet, 1947
    - User Copy, 1947 (Item 213)
  - The Medical Violet, 1948
    - User Copy, 1948 (Item 214)
  - The Medical Violet, 1949
    - User Copy, 1949 (Item 215)
  - The Medical Violet, 1950
    - User Copy, 1950 (Item 216)
  - The Medical Violet, 1951
    - User Copy, 1951 (Item 217)
  - The Medical Violet, 1952
    - User Copy, 1952 (Item 218)
  - The Medical Violet, 1953
    - User Copy, 1953 (Item 219)
  - The Medical Violet, 1954
    - User Copy, 1954 (Item 220)
  - The Medical Violet, 1955
    - User Copy, 1955 (Item 221)
  - The Medical Violet, 1956
    - User Copy, 1956 (Item 222)
  - The Medical Violet, 1957
    - User Copy, 1957 (Item 223)
  - The Medical Violet, 1958
    - User Copy, 1958 (Item 224)
  - The Medical Violet, 1959
    - User Copy, 1959 (Item 225)
  - The Medical Violet, 1960
    - User Copy, 1960 (Item 226)
  - The Medical Violet, 1961
    - User Copy, 1961 (Item 227)
  - The Medical Violet, 1962
    - User Copy, 1962 (Item 228)
  - The Medical Violet, 1963
    - User Copy, 1963 (Item 229)
  - The Medical Violet, 1964
    - User Copy, 1964 (Item 230)
  - The Medical Violet, 1965
    - User Copy, 1965 (Item 231)
  - The Medical Violet, 1966
    - User Copy, 1966 (Item 232)
  - The Medical Violet, 1967
    - User Copy, 1967 (Item 233)
  - The Medical Violet, 1968
    - User Copy, 1968 (Item 234)
  - The Medical Violet, 1969
    - User Copy, 1969 (Item 235)
  - The Medical Violet, 1970
    - User Copy, 1970 (Item 236)
  - The Medical Violet, 1971
    - User Copy, 1971 (Item 237)
  - The Medical Violet, 1972
    - User Copy, 1972 (Item 238)
  - The Medical Violet, 1973
    - User Copy, 1973 (Item 239)
  - The Medical Violet, 1974
    - User Copy, 1974 (Item 240)
  - The Medical Violet, 1975
    - User Copy, 1975 (Item 241)
  - The Medical Violet, 1976
    - User Copy, 1976 (Item 242)
  - The Medical Violet, 1977
    - User Copy, 1977 (Item 243)
  - The Medical Violet, 1978
    - User Copy, 1978 (Item 244)
  - The Medical Violet, 1979
    - User Copy, 1979 (Item 245)
  - The Medical Violet, 1980
    - User Copy, 1980 (Item 246)
  - The Medical Violet, 1981
    - User Copy, 1981 (Item 247)